People say you have to have a lot of passion for what you're doing, and it's totally true.
And the reason is because it's so hard that if you don't, any rational person would give up.
It's really hard, and you have to do it over a sustained period of time.
So if you don't love it, if you're not having fun doing it, if you don't really love it, you're going to give up.
And that's what happens to most people, actually.
If you really look at the ones that ended up being successful in the eyes of society, and the ones that didn't,
often times the ones that are successful loved what they did, so they could persevere when it got really tough.
And the ones that didn't love it quit. Who would want to put up with this stuff if you don't love it?
So it's a lot of hard work, and it's a lot of constant worry.
If you don't love it, you're going to fail. So you've got to love it. You've got to have passion.